One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Banquet Hall Third Floor Inside the Castle
Kalenin İçi Üçüncü Kat Ziyafet Salonu
Now then, I've got some samurai to snuff out.
Samurayları öldürme işi çıktı, gitmem lazım.
But before that, I ought to finish the job at hand.
Ona geçmeden önce, elimdeki işi çabucak bitirmeliyim.
Caiman Lady, are you ready to broadcast his voice all over the island?
Caiman Lady, sesini tüm adaya duyurmak için hazırlıklar tamam mı?
Yes, I am!
Evet, efendim.
Black Leg...
Kara Bacak...
Would you kindly summon Nico Robin at once?
Nico Robin'i buraya çağırır mısın?
We're all ready to go...
Hepimiz hazırız.
The Honorable Hyogoro "the Flower"
Onurlu "Çiçek" Hyogoro
I've set up layers of webbing all around the entrance.
Girişe, yapıştı mı bırakmayan...
Once you've touched my sticky, hard gum, you'll never escape.
bir ton ağ yerleştirilmiş durumda.
I've coated the floor as well.
Zemine de tabii.
One wrong step and you're trapped.
Tek bir adımla mahsur kalırsın.
On top of that, my girls are standing guard with tranquilizer guns in the back.
Ayrıca kızlarım da sakinleştirici silahlarıyla ötesinde bekliyor.
All that's left for you to do...
Geriye...
is call out for her!
Nico Robin'i...
Call Nico Robin!
çağırman kaldı!
Come on, call for help!
Hadi, yardım iste!
I have another matter to attend to!
Yapacak başka bir işim daha var!
Robin...
Robin-chan...
I want... to join your crew.
Tayfana katılmama izin ver.
– Huh?!
– Ha?!
I...
Ben...
I want to live!
Yaşamak istiyorum!
You sure are stubborn...
İnatçı çıktın sen de.
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Hadi! Hadi! Hadi!
Oh, I can't watch...
İzlemeye dayanamıyorum!
I'm going to cry...
Gözyaşlarım akıp duruyor!
That man won't let his friend come to harm!
Dostunu korumaya çalışıyor belli ki!
He'd rather die than utter a single word!
Ağzından tek kelime çıkmadan ölecek!
If he wasn't our enemy, I might have fallen in love!
Düşmanımız olmasaydı abayı yakmıştım!
W-Wait!
B-Bekle!
Give me a minute...
Bana bir iki kelime...
to say a few words...
söyleme fırsatı tanı!
I bet he just wants to say something like "eat shit" before he dies!
Ölmeden son bir küfretmek istiyor belli ki!
Please don't!
Yapma!
Don't make her any angrier, or else...
Onu daha da kızdıracaksın!
Robin...
Robin-chan...
I... I...
Ben... Ben...
I...
Ben...
wanted to see your smile... one more time...
gülümsemeni tekrar görmek istedim.
Help me, Robin!
Kurtar beni, Robin-chan!
– What?!
– Ne?!
He called her for help after all!
Çağıracak kıvama gelmiş meğerse!
I'm on the third floor!
Üçüncü kattaki...
In the banquet hall!
ziyafet salonundayım!
I've been taken hostage!
Rehin alındım!
I'm sorry!
Üzgünüm!
Sanji...
Sanji...
They're gonna kill me if you don't come, Robin!
Robin-chan, gelmezsen canımdan olacağım!
Help!
Kurtar beni!
What the hell is that? Talk about pathetic!
Bu yalvarış da ne böyle?
Is that one of the Straw Hats?!
Hasır Şapkalar'dan biri değil mi bu?
Listen to that! His voice is echoing across the entire island!
Hayda. Adanın her yerinden duyuluyor.
Nico Robin is one of the most important figures in the world.
Nico Robin, dünyanın en önemli kişilerinin başında geliyor.
They must be after her knowledge!
Demek bilgi birikiminin peşindeler.
Sounds to me like an obvious trap for Robin!
Robin'i yakalamak için tuzak olduğu açık!
Those are some pretty pathetic sounds coming from a man!
Erkek adam böyle ses çıkarır mı?
These guys are a riot!
Çok eğlenceli bir grup.
I'd bet anything it's a woman.
Düşman muhtemelen kadın.
What a pain...
Hep aynı terane.
Hey, Nami! His voice is coming from up there!
Hey, Nami! Sesi şuradan geliyor!
Be careful!
Dikkatli ol!
I saw one of those earlier!
Demin de bir tane gördüm.
You're my only hope!
Tek umudum sensin!
What's with that eye?
Bu göz ne ki?
Come quickly!
Acele gel...
Robin!
Robin-chan!
What a surprise.
İnanılmaz.
I called for Robin.
Robin'i çağırdım,
Now, untie me.
çöz artık beni.
What?!
Ne?
Madame, someone's coming!
Abla, biri geliyor!
Already, huh?
Çok çabuk oldu.
You're not going anywhere.
Seni serbest bırakmayacağım.
Huh?!
Heh?!
Didn't you say you loved me?
Beni sevdiğini söyledin.
Well, that means this isn't business anymore.
Artık mesele işten ziyade...
Now it's personal.
aşk oldu.
See those boys?
Seni de onlar gibi...
You'll be one of my precious pets, just like them.
evcil hayvanım yapmak istiyorum.
You won't be able to live without my touch once I'm through with you.
Seni bensiz yaşayamayacak bir hâle sokacağım.
– My heart belongs to Madame Black Maria alone...
– Kalbim yalnızca Black Maria-sama'ya aittir...
My heart...
Benim kalbim...
belongs to all the ladies!
tüm kadınlara aittir!
I forbid you to be unfaithful to me!
İhaneti affetmem!
You need to be disciplined!
Cezalandırılman gerek!
Hold on!
Bekle!
I wouldn't want to hurt a lady, so my armament haki is going soft!
Bir kadını incitmek istemediğimden silahlanma hakim devreye girmiyor!
Mil Fleurs!
Bin Çiçek!
Gigantesco Mano!
Devasa El...
Spank!
Tokadı!
Madame Black Maria!
Black Maria-sama!
How did you get in here?!
Nereden girdin sen?
I can bloom anywhere.
Her yerden filizlenebilirim.
How dare you strike my face...
Ne cüretle yüzüme vurursun?
You really thought I'd be so naive as to walk straight into your trap?
Şuna yem atayım da kolayca yakalarım mı zannettin?
Robin!
Robin-chan!
I spent a lot of time in nefarious organizations.
Ömrüm şer odaklı örgütlerle geçti.
When someone torments my friends...
Dostlarıma elini sürersen...
I can't contain...
içimdeki...
the devil within me!
şeytanı görürsün.
Ah, pardon me!
Affedersin!
I've cut you free with the icy chill of the underworld.
Ölüler diyarının ayazıyla bağlarını kestim!
Brook!
Brook!
Miss! They took down the tranquilizer unit!
Abla, sakinleştirici takımı yok edilmiş!
All your spider silk traps...
Ağ tuzakları da...
...have been frozen and shattered, too!
buz kesip kırılmış!
It seems as though spider silk and the chill of the underworld go well together!
Örümcek ağlarıyla yeraltı ayazının uyumu mükemmel.
Monsters!
Canavarlar!
– Look who's talking!
– Diyene bak!
Thank you!
Sağ ol.
You saved me...
Sayende kurtuldum.
Think nothing of it.
Rica ederim.
Sorry about this, but I'm gonna go lend a hand to Kin'emon's group!
Kusura bakmazsanız ben Kin'emonlara yardıma gideceğim.
For some reason, I just can't see myself winning this one!
Neden bilmiyorum ama burada kazanma şansım yok sanırım.
– You don't say.
– Haklısın.
Get back here, Black Leg!
Bekle, Kara Bacak!
You're going to be my pet!
Sen benim evcil hayvanımsın!
I won't let you go!
Bırakmam seni!
Is that all?
Son sözlerin...
Any more last words?
bunlar mı?
You'd die to save a man who'd sell out his own friends?
Dostunu satan bir kalleş için hayatını mı vereceksin?
No, Black Maria...
Hayır, Black Maria.
It seems you fail to understand...
Senin anlayabileceğin bir konu değil.
just how wonderful friends can be.
Dostlar harikadır.
Sanji!
Sanji!
Thank you for relying on me!
Bana güvendiğin için sağ ol.
It makes me happy!
Mutlu oldum.
Ah, watch out.
Dikkat et,
The floor is frozen.
zemin buzla kaplı.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Dur, dur, dur!
Thank you!
Sağ ol!
Forbidden Storeroom Inside the Dome
Kubbenin İçi Yasaklı Depo
Why would there be smoke coming out of a mouse?
Fareden neden duman çıkıyor ki?
It's one of the Marys, the surveillance unit of my father's army.
Babamın gözetleme birliği "Maryler"in üyesi bu.
It's a cyborg.
Sayborgdurlar.
In other words, an animal with mechanical body parts.
Bazı yerleri makineleşmiş hayvanlar.
What?!
Ne diyorsun?
They wander around the island aimlessly,
Adada başıboş dolaşır...
but they share what they see with the human Marys!
ve gördüklerini insan Maryler'e aktarırlar.
– What?!
– Ne?!
So, even in here...
Yani bu yer...
Hey, are you sure it's this storehouse?
Cidden buradalar mı?
This place is cursed. No one goes in there anymore.
Burası artık kimsenin adım atmadığı lanetli bir yer.
It doesn't look like anyone went inside.
Birinin girdiğine dair bir iz de yok.
But they said this was the place!
Ama burayı dediler.
There's no doubt about it!
Genç Efendi Yamato...
Young Master Yamato–
kesin burada–
I mean, the next shogun is in there!
Geleceğin Şogun-sama'sı yani!
It sounds like there are many of them.
Çok kalabalıklar.
This place isn't safe anymore!
Burası artık güvenli değil.
We must flee, Yamato!
Kaçalım, Yamato!
Please show us a path that keeps Lord Momonosuke out of sight!
Momonosuke-sama'ya gözlerden ırak tutacak bir yol göster.
Shogun! Come on out!
Şogun-sama, dışarı çıkın!
Or else we'll bash the door in!
Yoksa kapıyı kıracağız!
– One, two!
– Bir, iki!
They're breaking through!
Kapı fazla dayanmaz!
Sorry, Momonosuke!
Üzgünüm, Momonosuke-kun!
What?!
Ne?!
Hide in my clothes!
İçimde saklanman lazım!
What?
Ne?
Whaaat?!
Neee?!
Let's go, Shinobu!
Gidelim, Shinobu-san!
I told you to keep him out of their sight!
Gözlerden ırak tutalım demiştim!
I know!
Biliyorum!
They'll see him if we don't take them all down!
Hepsini devirmezsek bizi görürler!
That is not what I meant!
Bunu kastetmemiştim!
– Damn you!
– Aşağılık!
W-We Gifters have this route blocked already!
Y-Yetenekliler olarak yola barikat kurduk.
You really shouldn't be fighting yet!
Henüz savaşacak durumda değilsiniz.
Silence!
Kes lan!
Out of my way!
Çekilin yolumdan!
Bao Huang!
Bao Huang!
Are the Red Scabbards samurai still in the treasury?
Kızıl Kınlar hâlâ hazine odasında mı?
Yes, they are!
Oradalar.
Black Maria! Where are you now?!
Black Maria, şu an neredesin?
I'm still in the banquet hall.
Hâlâ ziyafet salonundayım.
Alright! I'll go and finish off those samurai!
Tamam, samurayların işini bitirmeye ben gidiyorum.
Even on the brink of death, there's no way in hell the Soaring Six can kill them!
Ağır yaralı olsalar da Tobi Roppo'nun öldüreceği kadar zayıf da değiller.
Got it?! Stay out of this!
Anladınız mı? Siz bir şey yapmayın!
Jack...
Jack...
You're underestimating me...
Bizi küçümsüyor...
Although...
Fakat...
this works out in my favor.
işime gelir.
Sweet Entanglement
Zevk Sarmalı
I appreciate him taking care of that for me.
Beni zahmetten kurtarır.
What in the world... is that?
O nedir?
Listen, Nico Robin...
Baksana Nico Robin...
You'll belong to Viceroy Kaido soon...
Sen Kaido-sama'nın...
It's inevitable.
olacaksın.
No, thanks.
İstemez.
I'd rather die!
Ölmeyi yeğlerim.
So cool!
Çok fiyakalı!
Onigashima Entrance
Onigashima Giriş
You gave it your best, full-moon warriors!
Yazık size dolunay savaşçıları.
Too bad the weather's not on your side!
Kazanmanız hava durumuna bağlı.
Pedro...
Pedro...
Listen!
Dinleyin!
You-gara must press on!
Siz-gara ilerlemeye devam etmelisiniz!
No matter what... I have to avenge Pedro...!
Mutlaka Pedro'nun öcünü alacağım!
Avenge Pedro?!
Pedro'nun öcünü almak mı?
That worthless fool deserved to die!
O göt ölmeyi hak etti.
What was your plan after waltzing into the Big Mom Pirates' territory? Have a picnic?!
Big Mom Korsanları'nın bölgesine piknik falan mı yapmaya geldiniz?
If you don't want your friends to die, why don't you go back to grazing in the forest?!
Dostlarının ölümünü görmek istemiyorsan git ormanında otlan!
You can lick your wounds there!
Senin yerin orası-perorin.
Now then...
Bakalım.
This alliance with the Beast Pirates doesn't bring me a lick of excitement...
Canavar Korsanları'yla ittifak kurmaktan hoşnut olmasam da...
but it's Mama's decision, so I guess it can't be helped...
emir büyük yerden. Katlanacağız.
We need to teach these kids that the Four Emperors are way out of their league!
Şu kendini bilmezlere Yonkoların seviyesini göstereyim.
They're running!
Kaçıyorlar!
The enemy leader Momonosuke...
Düşmanların lideri Momonosuke,
is moving away from...
yasaklı depodan...
the Forbidden Storeroom!
kaçtı!
I cannot see Momonosuke at the moment!
Momonosuke'yi göremiyorum!
But there can be no doubt!
Ama şüphesiz...
Momonosuke is with Young Master Yamato and the kunoichi!
Momonosuke, Genç Efendi Yamato'yla kadın ninjanın yanında!
Momonosuke General of Wano's Samurai
Wano'nun Samuray Ordusunun Lideri Momonosuke
It may be cramped and hard to breathe, but for whatever reason...
Daracık ve nefes alması zor bir yerde olsam da...
I feel as though I am in heaven!
niyeyse mutluluktan havaya uçacağım!
Shinobu, this way!
Shinobu-san, bu taraftan!
They just keep coming!
Ardı arkası kesilmiyor!
We need to find a less visible route!
Artık gözlerden ırak kalacak bir yol göstersen mi?
Don't worry!
Rahat ol sen!
They can't see us if we take them all out!
Hepsini devirirsek gözlerden ırak oluruz!
Like I told you, that is not what I meant!
O anlamda demedim ben be!
I repeat!
Tekrarlıyorum!
Momonosuke, who escaped from the Forbidden Storehouse,
Yasaklı depodan kaçan Momonosuke...
Third Floor Inside the Castle
Kalenin İçi Üçüncü Kat
is with Young Master Yamato and the kunoichi!
kesin Genç Efendi Yamato'yla kadın ninjanın..
For certain!
yanında!
Another broadcast...
Yine mi o yayın?
They're going after Momo and Shinobu!
Momo'yla Shinobu-chan'ın peşindeler.
Young Master Yamato?
Genç Efendi Yamato kim?
Well, whatever...
Neyse.
Hey, which way is the Forbidden Storehouse?!
Cevap ver. Yasaklı depo ne tarafta?
L-Like I'm gonna tell you.
B-Beni konuşturamazsın!
Huh?!
Heh?!
I-It's near the entrance of the Skull Dome...
Kuru Kafa Kubbesi'nin girişinde...
Kin'emon's group is at the back of the castle tower...
Kin'emonlar kale kulesinin arkasında.
Dome Entrance Back of the Castle Tower
Kubbe Girişi Kale kulesinin arkası
That's in the opposite direction of the Dome's entrance.
Kubbe girişinin tersinde kalıyor.
Kin'emon and the others are hurting bad...
Dövüşten ağır yaralı ayrılan Kin'emonlar.
Momo and Shinobu are being chased by the damn Gifters...
Yetenekliler'in peşine düştüğü Momo'yla Shinobu-chan.
Which of them needs me more?!
Hangisine yardım etsem?
This way?! That way?!
Bu taraf mı, o taraf mı?
No time to think!
Niye tereddüt ediyorum?
The ones who need me the most are...
Bana en çok ihtiyaç duyanlar...
definitely this way!
kesinlikle bu tarafta!
I can't...
Buraya kadar.
This blue flame draws out my stamina, but...
Bu mavi alevler gücümüzü korumamıza yardımcı oldu ama...
I think that I am...
artık dayanma gücüm...
almost at my limit...
kalmadı!
Fight it! Or you'll turn into an ice ogre again!
Dayan! Yoksa yeniden buz şeytanına dönüşeceksin!
You'll lose control, use up the rest of your energy, and die for sure this time!
Sonra da dermanın bitene kadar etrafa saldıracak ve bu kez öleceksin!
Don't give up, young man!
Pes etme, delikanlı!
Get a hold of yourself!
İradene sarıl!
That tanuki is suffering the same pain as you, but he's still working hard on the antidote!
O Tanuki-san da aynı acıyla kıvranıyor ama hâlâ şifa arıyor!
How could we give up before him?
Pes edip emeğini hiç mi edelim?
B-Big Boss...
P-Patron...
You look different...
bu hâliniz...
Leave it to this old man!
Burayı bu ihtiyara bırakın.
It's time to show them...
Bir samurayın...
a samurai's resilience!
metanetini sergileme vaktidir!
Apoo, we can't fight anymore!
Apoo-san, daha fazla dayanamayacağız!
The antibody is right behind them, but we just can't break through their ironclad defense!
Antikor arkalarında olsa da kale gibi savunuyorlar, aşamıyoruz!
Why would His Awesomeness infect us too?! We're on his side!
Aynı tarafta olduğumuz hâlde Queen-sama niye bize de virüs bulaştırdı?
He's not gonna save you no matter how much you bitch and moan!
Ağlamayana meme vermez o!
Just kill that tanuki and get the antibody already!
Gidip şu tanukiyi gebertin ve antikoru geri alın!
Dammit!
Tüküreyim!
Drake! That traitor!
Drake! Hain piç!
Stop acting like a hero!
Gelmiş şimdi kahramanlık ayakları yapıyor.
Drake isn't the only problem!
Tek sorun Drake de değil.
That withered old man recovered somehow!
Ruhunu teslim etmek üzere olan moruk bir anda ayağa kalktı!
The legendary boss of Wano's underworld!
Wano'nun efsanevi yakuza patronu...
X Drake Former Soaring Six Member Saur-Saur Fruit: Allosaurus Hyogoro "the Flower" Legendary Boss of the Underworld
X Drake Tobi Roppo'nun Eski Üyesi Ejderha-Ejderha Meyvesi Antik Model: Allosaurus "Çiçek" Hyogoro Wano'nun Efsanevi Yakuza Patronu
Hyogoro the Flower!
Çiçek Hyogoro!
With those two monsters standing guard...
İki hayvani bekçileri var.
we have no chance of getting to that tanuki!
Tanukiye gram yaklaşamıyoruz!
Why does he look like that?!
Bu hâl de ne?
He was just a little old man a second ago!
Az önce cücük kadardı!
He's changed back into the tower of a man that Kaido was dead set on recruiting!
Kaido'nun kapısını aşındırdığı güçlü zamanlarına döndü!
Shaking with excitement, huh?
Heyecandan titriyorum.
Big Boss!
Patron!
Are you okay?!
İyi misiniz?!
Yeah...
Evet.
I can feel a chill... however...
Donmaya başladım. Fakat...
I still have faith in my spirit!
irademe güveniyorum.
I suppose catching this virus...
Kazara virüse dokunmak...
drew out the last of my strength, leaving me within an inch of death.
beni ölümün eşiğine getirse de bütün gücümü açığa çıkardı!
So it's all come down to this...
Son raddedeyiz...
With my remaining power...
Kalan gücümle,
even if it costs me my life...
canım pahasına da olsa,
I will cut down every last one...
tüm kilit isimleri...
of their major players!
indireceğim!
Hey! Underbosses!
Hey! Sefirler!
– Yes, Big Boss!
– Buyur, Patron!
I may not have much time left...
Çok vaktim kalmadı.
If that tanuki can't finish the cure and I turn into an ice ogre...
Tanuki-san ilacı vaktinde bitiremez ve buz şeytanına dönüşürsem...
Do one thing for me first!
Dönüşümüm tamamlanmadan...
Don't hesitate...
tereddüt etmeyip....
to strike me down!
beni öldüresiniz!
If you don't...
Aksi takdirde...
I'll cut you all down...
sizi de...
every last person—friend or foe—
çevredekileri de...
until no one is left!
ayrım gözetmeksizin kesip biçeceğim!
How can we...
Elimiz gitmez!
But... if the big boss becomes an ice ogre...
Ama buz şeytanına dönüşürse...
nobody has a chance of stopping him...
kimsenin onu durduramayacağı da bir gerçek.
I'm counting on you...
Size güveniyorum.
Alright then...
Pekâlâ. Öyleyse...
As a former member of the Mimawari-gumi, I'd like to see what he's got...
eski Mimawari-gumi'ye yeteneklerini göster.
You're some kind of legend, huh?
Yesinler efsaneliğini.
All I see is a washed-up swordsman!
Sen yalnızca tarihi geçmiş bir kılıç ustasısın.
You old fart!
Seni bunak ihtiyar!
Prepare yourself!
Hazırla kendini!
One-Sword Style of the Flower!
Tek Kılıç Çiçek Stili:
Flaming Hair...
Kutsal Öfkenin...
of Holy Rage!
Alevli Saçları!
Flaming
Kutsal
Hair of
Öfkenin
Holy
Alevli
Rage
Saçları
Just throw bodies at him! Go!
Sayı avantajını kullanın! Yürüyün!
Hey, Oden...
Duyuyor musun Oden?
I sometimes wish...
Bazen diyorum keşke kudretimin...
that we had challenged Kaido back in the days...
yerinde olduğu zamanlara dönüp seninle omuz omuza Kaido'ya karşı...
when we were at our peaks.
savaşabilseydik.
But now...
Fakat şimdi...
Kin'emon and the others...
Kin'emonlar...
have pulled off the perfect raid!
başarılı bir baskın düzenledi.
Furthermore...
Hem...
I have gained a most interesting disciple!
benim de etkileyici bir çırağım oldu.
Sir Straw Hat!
Hasır şapkalı evlat,
You have great potential.
sende büyük bir cevher var.
You will continue to grow stronger and stronger!
Daha çok güçleneceksin.
Remember this.
Unutma.
In a moment of crisis...
Kriz anında...
your true power will be revealed!
hakiki gücün ortaya çıkar!
Let us take down Kaido together!
Kaido'yu devirelim!
You got it!
Bana güven!
Using that ryuo you taught me...
Senden öğrendiğim ryuo ile...
I'll kick Kaido's ass!
Kaido'yu tepeleyeceğim!
There was neither a hint of deception nor conceit in those words.
Sözlerinde ne yalan ne de kibir vardı.
I'm certain he'll master ryuo, grow even stronger...
Ryuoda ustalaşıp çok daha güçlü olacak...
and finally take down Kaido!
ve Kaido'yu devirecek.
Keep watching, Oden!
İyi seyret, Oden!
I know in my heart that the land of Wano...
Wano'da mutlaka...
will see the dawn once again!
şafak yeniden sökecek!
Whoa there!
Oba!
The whole floor is gonna get wiped out!
Salondaki tüm askerlerin işi bitmiş!
Time to meet your maker, you old fool!
Geber, moruk!
Phoenix Brand!
Anka Damgası!
You better keep your eyes on me, Queen!
Başka şeylere dalma, Queen!
Marco!
Marco!
That hurt!
Acıdı lan!
Was that a shockwave or something, you punk?!
Şok dalgası mıydı o? Seni piç!
I'm the one you're fighting right now!
Senin rakibin benim!
You can focus on attacking those samurai...
Samuraylara saldıracaksan...
after you chop off my head!
önce benim kellemi alman lazım-yoi!
Dammit! This guy just won't die!
Hay böyle işin... Çok oldun sen!
Go to hell already!
Geber git artık!
Bluebird!
Mavi Kuş!
Time to finish you off!
İşini bitireceğim senin...
You son of a bitch!
piçin evladı!
Don't push your luck!
Götün kalkmış belli!
Crane Talons!
Anka Pençesi!
Guess it's no surprise... Holding off a couple guys worth over a billion ain't easy...
Kafasında 1 milyondan fazla ödül olan iki kişiyi durdurmak sahiden çok zor.
You bastard!
Şerefsiz!
Come on already, tanuki...!
Acele et, tanuki!
What's this? Is that Marco I spy over there?
Bak sen... Marco değil mi şu?
Seems like he's taken a real...
Bitkin duruyor...
licking.
perorin.
Everyone's turning back into ice ogres!
Herkes tekrar buz şeytanına dönüştü!
Th-The fire's gone...
A-Alev söndü!
Help me!
Yardım edin!
Do it! This is what I want!
Yapın! Arzum budur!
It's as if the heavens themselves have granted me one final reward...
Âdeta cennetten bir armağan gibi.
I was rotting away in a cell, just waiting to die,
Hapse düşüp ölüme gün sayarken...
and yet I made it all the way here...
buralara kadar geldim!
However, if I continue to live, all of your lives are at risk!
Fakat artık sizin için tehlike arz ediyorum.
Forgive me for putting you in this position...
İnanın size böyle zor bir görev yüklemek istemezdim...
but you must do this for me!
ancak yapılmak zorunda.
The rest of you will have to carry on in my stead...
Gerisini size bırakıyorum.
The man known as Hyogoro the Flower...
Çiçek Hyogoro denen bu adam...
leaves this world...
içinde hiçbir pişmanlığı...
with no regrets!
olmadan ölüyor!